Hi, welcome to Marvelous Designer's asset creation tutorial.
In this tutorial, we will make a student backpack.
First, we will load a virtual model from the library window, and use it to determine the size of the backpack.
Download our default T-shirt and pants, select the automatically adjusted version, and start making the backpack after the version is automatically modified.
Move all the versions in the 2D window to the side.
Select the rectangular tool and create half of the version based on the model screenshot in the 2D window.
Then use the
In the tool group in the edit tab, select the vertical point in the lower right corner of the original version, drag it to make it a rectangle.
In the tool group in the edit tab, find the plus point division tool, on the top right of the line, open the partition window.
In the window, select an average segment, the number of lines is 4, and click OK to see three dots.
Then switch to the edit panel tool, right-click on the newly created point just now, and choose to convert it to a free curve point.
Select the middle line, right-click and select Open.
In the 3D window, select the panel, use the positioning ball to place it behind the model.
Use the edit panel tool to select the middle panel, right-click and select Copy, then right-click on the appropriate position and select Paste to copy a similar panel.
Select the previous panel, right-click and select Level Rotate to turn it over.
Then right-click again and select Freeze Panel.
Use the positioning ball to copy and paste.
The selected panel is now behind the model.
Select the free curve tool to create a seam line between the two panels.
Press the control grid key on the keyboard to run the simulation.
The panel on the inside will be fixed in 3D space as a basis for fixing other panels.
Use the delete button to delete the extra straight lines from theTM confident on the arrangement panel to add a cutting edge to the panel.
Use the delete tool to find the long edge at the bottom of the panel.
Then press the Q to enter fromlles to female number 3, tpaw 1, the height of the panel is 110.
USE Shift to select curving stitches on the lowerShell, withoroGH to set the length.
Use the где table to locate where the width of the panel was set, find the length.
Use the raise each to match the center line.
Next, we will adjust the position of the panels in the 2D window.
Select the two panels that have been newly created and move them to the right position in the 3D window.
Click on the panel, follow the position of the 3D window, use the positioning ball to rotate it to the right position.
Please note that the panels should be facing inward.
Select the free sewing tool to create a sewing line between the side panels and the backpack panels.
Sewing while observing the sewing line in the 3D window to ensure that the sewing line is in the right direction.
Select the panel you just frozen, right-click, select copy and paste, and copy a similar panel.
This panel will become the front of the bag, so I need to untangle it, and then use the free sewing tool to sew it together with the side panels.
When all panels are combined, use the adjustment panel tool to select all the bag panels, right-click, select hardening, then press the control button to start modeling.
Select all panels other than the frozen panels, and then select the panel you just frozen.
Select the panel you just frozen, and then press the control button to start modeling.
Select all panels other than the frozen panels.
In the attribute editor, change their pressure to 1, and then start modeling.
The bag will bulge, and this step is complete.
Now we will create the pocket on the side of the bag.
Select the edit panel tool, press the Shift key to select the two sides of the side panel.
To create an internal line
According to the value you entered
You can preview the position of the internal line
Here I entered 180mm
After confirmation
On the internal line created, right-click
Choose to cut and sew
Now you will see
The board has been cut off
Next, we will build a pocket board
Based on the cut board
Use the adjustment board tool
Select the next small board
And copy and paste a board
Place the created pocket board
In the 3D window
To the corresponding position of the pocket
Use the edit board tool
Select this line at the top
Move it so that the pocket board becomes wider
Then select this line on the left
Press the right arrow key on the keyboard
This line will move 10mm
To reduce the height of the pocket board
Every time you move the element through the direction key
It is moved by 10mm
As a unit
Now select the border of the two sides and bottom of the pocket
Right-click and select the expansion of the pocket board
Set the diameter to 20mm
And select the corner as the side angle
Then select the corner as the side angle
Select the extra point
Press the delete key to delete
Now we will use the free sewing tool
Sew the pocket board to the side panel
After sewing the other lines one by one
Please pay attention to the side sewing line of the pocket
Sew to the blue reference point
That is, the equal length position
To create the fold of the top of the pocket
Use the edit board tool
Select this line on the left
Right-click and select the internal line diameter
Set the diameter to 20mm
Create a new line
In the element editor on the right
Select the flexible
We will set the flexible ratio to 50
For the outer line of the tablet
Set the same value
Use the edit board tool
Select the board
Press the button to print
Then press the control button to start the simulation
After the simulation is stable
Press the button to remove the print
Then go to the element editor
Reduce the particle diameter from 20 to 10
Simulate
Then reduce to 5
Simulate again
In the element editor
Increase the thickness of the reference
Then increase the thickness of the reference
In the element editor
Increase the thickness of the reference
Increase it to 2
To increase the visual thickness of the pocket
Then adjust the pressure of the pocket panel
to 0
If you need to check the thickness
Please open the density pattern surface
in the try to display menu
If you want to create the same pocket on the other side
We can use the edit board tool
Select the pocket panel
Then select the copy option in the menu bar on the right, then select the mirror paste option to create a mirror-to-line version.
Similarly, use the free sewing tool to complete the sewing line.
Select the version and press the right button to print and then simulate.
After selecting the version in the 3D window, press the right button to stop printing.
After confirming that the versions are all sewed together, use the edit version tool to select one of the internal lines, then press the right button to cut the seam allowance.
Open the simulation and confirm that the two pockets have been adjusted.
Now we will create a pocket with a lid on the front of the backpack.
Select the edit version tool, click on the bottom line of the front of the bag, press the right button to cut the inner line to create the inner line for subsequent separation.
I will set the seam allowance to 70mm.
On the inner line created, press the right button to select the cut seam allowance.
Then select the line cut out and use the inner line seam allowance function again.
This time we enter 160mm as the seam allowance.
Use the right button again to select the cut seam allowance function on the menu bar.
To create a pocket with a lid on the zipper part, we need to select the cut out version again, then select the inner line seam allowance.
Enter 40mm as the seam allowance.
Select this inner line, then select the cut seam allowance.
Use the edit version tool to select the middle version to create the zipper cover.
Press the right button to open the menu bar.
Then, press the button to select the side- tournaments.
Use the click Mmmm button to select the overriding- osob.
Using the click Mmmm button, we see the overriding-obs serve the first and second snowmen.
Press the Hoch barrier button to select the its top-end part and up the bottom part.
To create the side of the cover, we select these three edges, then click the right button to select the expansion of the outside of the panel
We set the diameter to 10mm
Use the edit panel tool to delete the excess points
Refer to the video to complete the sewing line
Please note that if you need to merge multiple lines and one line together
When creating the sewing line, select one line first, then press the Shift key
When you see the sewing line turn yellow, start to select multiple lines on the other side
Press the Shift key and select multiple sections at a time, merge to the blue point position, and then the other side is the same operation
Select one line from the menu
Select the panel, press the right button to select the hardening, then simulate
After the simulation is complete, press the right button to select the hardening
After checking the simulation is stable, select the side panel and front panel of the bag, apply hardening, then simulate
Then gradually reduce its particle diameter from 20 to 5
Pressure value needs to be reduced to 0
Now we will create the pocket and bag cover on the front panel
Select the inner rectangle tool in the internal shape creation group
And draw the appropriate shape on the front panel
If you need to create a square, please press the Shift key during the drag
Use the collocation outline tool in the edit panel tool group
Select the inner shape just drawn, then press the right button to collocate as a panel
segregate and duplicate bottke
With the only standard of color, press mx position.
Use the ocher profile tool to dependent the animal Navigate the dog
By using setting slices tool, select a new feel sheet
Then duplicate the same sal e sheet
In the 3D window, switch the fashion display style to a black and white surface
Select the pocket flat sheet, select the horizontal flip
Then move them into the penis's outside
When placing, place the bottom panel near the inner line of the pocket, and the other panel above it.
First, use the edit panel tool to shorten the length of the cover.
When dragging the bottom line, press the mouse button to enter 40mm as the moving distance.
Choose the pocket panel, select the top line, press the direction button to shorten the pocket by 10mm.
Then select the side line and bottom line, and in the menu on the right-hand side, select Expand Outline.
Then select the five corners and enter 20 in the border.
Delete the excess points as before.
Use the free sewing tool to sew.
To ensure that the corners are the same, press the mouse button to enter 40mm as the moving distance.
To ensure that the corners are the same, press the mouse button to enter 20 in the border.
Then continue to use the free sewing tool to sew
Click on these lines without the sewing line, then press the right button to create the inner line, I will enter the inner line as 10
Press the right button to select the cut-off sewing
We will use the adjustment panel tool to re-arrange the panels in the 2D window
Select these panels through the adjustment panel tool, press the right button to select hardening, then simulate
Wait for the simulation to stabilize, select these panels, and then press the right button to select hardening
Then gradually reduce the particle diameter from 20 to 5 to get a better simulation
Increase the thickness of these panels in the property editor
Set the thickness of the edge of the cover to 2 mm, then set the thickness of the inner panel to 1 mm
Use the inner rectangle tool to draw the inner rectangle used to sew the cover and pocket, then copy and paste it on the pocket
Then Integration
Use the fascination tool to sew the same line together
After the simulation, check the effect in the 3D window, you can use adjustment panel tool
while choosing both pattern and size, move to the desired position
Then we copy the inner line of the pocket, paste it next to it, and start making another pocket
Then select all the components of the pocket on the left side, and in the menu in the right-hand corner, select Copy-Paste to create a pocket on the right-hand side
Now we have completed the creation of the other side of the pocket
Create a sewing line in the same way as before
Then repeat the previous operation to make the top pocket
This time, Question orот will be on both the bottom-right of the pocket and top-left corner of the pocket
Create the same on all documents
Eliminate the wrong-icial Abraham
Started